‎SPOOKY IN LOVE
‎It's my fault.
‎Because of me…
‎EPISODE 5
‎Mr. Ma?
‎Gang-uk.
‎Oh, no…
‎Because of me,
‎you turned into a ghost already
‎and came to see me?
‎Oh, no…
‎Oh, gosh…
‎I'm not a ghost.
‎I'm alive.
‎But before, I definitely saw you…
‎Gang-uk!
‎-Charge to 200 joules.
‎-Charging to 200.
‎-Clear.
‎-Mr. Ma!
‎Mr. Ma.
‎Clear.
‎It worked. We have a pulse.
‎He's back. He's okay.
‎You're alive?
‎Are you sure you're really alive?
‎I am.
‎My head hurts a bit,
‎but I'm quite all right
‎for someone who got hit by a car.
‎I thought you'd actually died
‎because of me.
‎Do you know how scared I was?
‎I'm sorry.
‎You're not hurt anywhere, right?
‎Mr. Ma!
‎You need to come.
‎-Is there something wrong?
‎-No.
‎There's nothing
‎terribly wrong with him right now,
‎but the doctor wants to run
‎a few tests, just in case.
‎That gave us all quite a scare.
‎You still seem to be in shock.
‎We should get going then.
‎Take good care of Mr. Ma for us.
‎You go on ahead.
‎-I don't mind staying behind.
‎-What?
‎It's been a long day. Go on home.
‎It's late, and your wife will be worried.
‎Why would she worry
‎with everything that's happening?
‎One of us should stay behind.
‎Yes, that one person…
‎What? Oh, she's…
‎-She's going to stay?
‎-Yes.
‎-Yes, she's staying.
‎-She is?
‎Take good care of him for us. Thank you.
‎-At least until he falls asleep…
‎-Take care.
‎Hey.
‎Drink lots of water to flush
‎the contrast medium out of your system.
‎You'll be hospitalized for the night,
‎and the doctor will give you the results
‎in the morning.
‎Okay. Thank you.
‎You're welcome.
‎CT IMAGING ROOM
‎You're still here, Yeo-ri?
‎The one month isn't up yet.
‎It's not over until the moon
‎disappears at dawn.
‎Try to keep up.
‎Okay.
‎They agreed not to come into your room.
‎How did you make them agree to that?
‎I told them the usual,
‎that they can come to my place
‎if they really want to talk.
‎Did this happen
‎because we celebrated a day early?
‎What's meant to happen happens,
‎regardless of such things.
‎Only seeing and hearing
‎what everyone else does…
‎I can't believe
‎that's something worth celebrating.
‎Yeo-ri.
‎The moon will set soon.
‎You must be exhausted, so go home.
‎I'd rather stay where I can be at ease
‎than go home and be anxious.
‎Your month is almost up for good,
‎so I'll rest here with you.
‎I didn't get to ask you
‎because things got a bit hectic.
‎Why did Park Seung-jae abduct you?
‎I'm the one who put him behind bars.
‎I think he caught on to my secret.
‎But how?
‎That's a family matter.
‎How did you know where to find me anyway?
‎Well…
‎FIND ME
‎I think a ghost told me.
‎-A ghost?
‎-Yes.
‎Come in.
‎Hello.
‎-I'm here to change your IV bag.
‎-Okay.
‎Can you be gentle this time?
‎It hurt earlier.
‎-I'm scared of needles.
‎-Okay.
‎HANKUK NATIONAL UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
‎Because of me,
‎you turned into a ghost already
‎and came to see me?
‎Oh, no…
‎I think the one month is up now.
‎I should go do some stretching.
‎REGIONAL EMERGENCY MEDICAL CENTER
‎I told you I'd be fine.
‎You didn't have to worry.
‎Still, I feel much better
‎after seeing the results myself.
‎I guess today is day one
‎of not seeing ghosts.
‎Yes, based on my experiences so far.
‎I really won't see them
‎anymore, right?
‎I find it really hard to believe,
‎but knowing such supernatural beings
‎exist in our world today…
‎I know, right?
‎Anyway, congratulations.
‎You can go back to your normal life now.
‎I feel bad that I'm the only one
‎who gets off like this.
‎Don't be.
‎It's a relief that you, at least,
‎can escape this fate.
‎Yeo-ri.
‎Even if you were to
‎continue seeing ghosts,
‎that wouldn't mean I'd stop seeing them.
‎We can't shake hands anymore,
‎so let's part ways here.
‎From now on,
‎let's never cross paths again.
‎Take care.
‎Thanks for everything.
‎REHEAT THE RICE AND SOUP AND EAT WELL
‎From now on,
‎let's never cross paths again.
‎Take care.
‎Thanks for everything.
‎Just to be clear,
‎I never told you to kidnap her.
‎And don't call me like this again,
‎not even through your lawyer.
‎Wait, Ha-ri, I--
‎Hello? Cheon Ha-ri!
‎Damn it.
‎The assemblyman said
‎he can't help you anymore.
‎He told me to inform you
‎that there'd be no more favors.
‎Wait…
‎Damn it.
‎Mr. Ma. Are you all right?
‎I'm still a bit sore. Did you have lunch?
‎I told you I put in a day off for you.
‎Why are you so stubborn?
‎Come on, there's a warrant hearing later.
‎I told you the chief prosecutor
‎can handle that for you.
‎-Mr. Ma.
‎-Yeah?
‎You need to see this.
‎Why?
‎What is it?
‎PARK SEUNG-JAE ABDUCTED CEO CHEON YEO-RI,
‎MOTIVE UNDER INVESTIGATION
‎Reporters are already
‎swarming outside Reina.
‎PARK SEUNG-JAE ABDUCTED CEO CHEON YEO-RI
‎Please leave.
‎We'll explain some other time.
‎Mr. Ma.
‎-She won't do any interviews.
‎-Just let us…
‎-No, you can't…
‎-Will you stop it?
‎-Just a few shots.
‎-No way!
‎-Stop! Get back!
‎-Don't take any photos!
‎-You can't.
‎-No photos or filming!
‎-Can we get a comment?
‎-No photos, please!
‎-What happened?
‎-Don't take photos!
‎-Is everything we heard true?
‎-I said, no photos.
‎-Any further comments?
‎-Just a brief statement, please.
‎Gosh, there are so many of them.
‎-How are you now?
‎-We won't take long.
‎-Any comments, please?
‎-Please stop.
‎-Can you tell us anything?
‎-Please step back.
‎-Excuse me, Ms. Cheon.
‎-Move back.
‎-Can you do an interview?
‎Are you dating Ms. Cheon?
‎Should there be
‎any unverified information,
‎speculative articles,
‎or photos distributed…
‎Reina will take strong legal action.
‎Direct your questions
‎to the secretaries' office,
‎and please step back.
‎I should've gotten here sooner.
‎Are you all right?
‎Yeah.
‎Thanks.
‎I'm sorry for causing you concern.
‎Were you hurt anywhere?
‎Should I call Dr. Kim?
‎Let's get you admitted for some tests.
‎No.
‎There's an inspection for the GA21 banquet
‎by the Ministry of Foreign Affairs today.
‎I came to work thinking only of that.
‎We'll take strong action
‎against not only Park Seung-jae,
‎but his father Assemblyman Park too.
‎Don't worry about them
‎and look after yourself.
‎Okay.
‎I do have more questions to ask you,
‎but let's leave it at that for today.
‎Just handle the inspection,
‎then go home and rest.
‎Don't worry about me, Grandma.
‎What is it?
‎What do you want?
‎What?
‎The secretaries confirmed it.
‎You visited Park Seung-jae in prison twice
‎before he kidnapped me.
‎Is that when you put him up to kidnap me?
‎What do you mean, kidnap you?
‎Even if I…
‎Yes, I did visit him.
‎But only because he begged me to.
‎I only went and saw him.
‎Park Seung-jae isn't
‎the tight-lipped type,
‎so I'm sure the investigation
‎will reveal everything.
‎Cheon Ha-ri.
‎You can tell a lot about a person
‎by what they do.
‎Take a long, hard look
‎at everything you've done so far,
‎because that's your future.
‎What do you mean?
‎You're not making any sense.
‎If you don't understand,
‎just memorize it.
‎"Don't do bad things."
‎Also,
‎I'm not letting this slide.
‎Don't think I did.
‎Was Ha-ri behind it?
‎She did visit him in prison,
‎but that doesn't prove anything.
‎By the way, what are you doing in Seoul?
‎That took you long enough.
‎I called you as soon as I arrived.
‎G1A Group is trying to sell Fiel Seoul.
‎-Is CL going to acquire it?
‎-Yeah.
‎It's the only big resort brand
‎in the northern Seoul area.
‎I heard their debt ratio
‎is on the higher side.
‎That's true,
‎but we have a financial arm
‎that can handle the aftermath.
‎Anyway, do you know how shocked I was
‎during my breakfast meeting?
‎First, it was in Jeju Island,
‎and now this.
‎Things keep going wrong.
‎What happened in Jeju was on us.
‎I think I'll be in Seoul
‎until the acquisition is finalized.
‎You'll call me, right?
‎What?
‎I knew it.
‎You owe me a meal.
‎Right.
‎Yes, of course.
‎Well, when are you free?
‎Instead of going somewhere to eat,
‎you can accompany me elsewhere.
‎Yeeon Museum of Art.
‎They're unveiling an artifact
‎they excavated recently.
‎I have a meeting there
‎that my mother arranged.
‎Yeeon?
‎The director there is pretty influential.
‎This new artifact should interest you too,
‎since it's not entirely unrelated
‎to your major.
‎What is it?
‎I'll send you a link
‎to the director's interview.
‎From what my mom told me,
‎she seems to be seeing
‎some prosecutor pretty often.
‎Yes, Secretary Oh.
‎I need you to look into someone for me.
‎Prosecutor Ma Gang-uk from the Seoul
‎Central District Prosecutors' Office.
‎Min-hwan.
‎THE HOLY BIBLE
‎-So you've finally settled on one?
‎-No.
‎I went back to having no religion.
‎What?
‎I switched back.
‎I see.
‎I don't believe it.
‎Jeez.
‎Why did you want to see me?
‎How much do you know about Yeo-ri?
‎More than you think.
‎I doubt that.
‎You know she broke off her engagement
‎with the son of Cha & Yul's
‎managing partner, right?
‎I only heard about it
‎since I was abroad at the time.
‎Then do you know why they broke it off?
‎Do I have to know why?
‎You told me before
‎that if you care about someone,
‎you learn all about them.
‎I thought you'd naturally want to know
‎why they broke it off.
‎Don't you want to know?
‎Some rumors started
‎after the engagement fell through.
‎Ha-ri.
‎If I want to know something,
‎I can look into it myself.
‎Oh, that night at the hospital?
‎I remember.
‎You're where?
‎An anonymous tip-off
‎leading to the discovery of a body.
‎Doesn't it feel like ‎déjà vu?
‎Yes.
‎I don't need extra layers like these.
‎You should go inside and warm up.
‎Nice, we did it. High-five?
‎Lend me a hand?
‎-Enjoy your lunch.
‎-You too, sir.
‎-Enjoy your lunch, sir!
‎-Thank you.
‎Reina Hotel's slush fund allegations?
‎Yeah. I sense some rising smoke.
‎Rich people use art
‎to launder money, you know.
‎-It's pretty large-scale too.
‎-Come on.
‎It smoked a bit,
‎but the fire went out long ago.
‎Ma'am, have you
‎not been sleeping well lately?
‎Why do you ask?
‎You look very tired.
‎Who is that?
‎That's Director Lee Hwa-yong
‎of the Yeeon Foundation.
‎Yeeon Museum of Art.
‎The director there is pretty influential.
‎-Mr. Bong.
‎-Yes?
‎Could you come a little closer?
‎Pardon? Oh, sure.
‎The artworks displayed at the hotel
‎are brought in by the Art Team
‎through Director Ok,
‎so Gallery Cheon supplies them, right?
‎Yes, that is correct.
‎Have we ever made
‎a direct purchase from Yeeon?
‎No, not as far as I'm aware.
‎Would you like me to look into it?
‎No, I'll bring it up some other time.
‎Don't stand too close.
‎Oh, right.
‎A 300-year-old love letter
‎written by Joseon-era
‎courtesan-turned-poet Hwagyeongdang,
‎whose story was likened
‎to the 1990 film ‎Ghost
‎recently came to light.
‎It recently became the talk of the town.
‎We asked Lee Hwa-yong,
‎the director of Yeeon Foundation,
‎why she decided
‎to reveal the letter to the public.
‎Well…
‎We discovered this love letter
‎while relocating the tomb
‎of my ancestor, Prince Gangpyeong.
‎As many are already aware,
‎the letter shows
‎Hwagyeongdang's ‎love ‎for Prince Gangpyeong
‎that transcended class and social status.
‎These days, there's so much violence
‎carried out in the name of love,
‎so I wanted to remind us
‎what's most important
‎and provide consolation
‎in what little way I can
‎by displaying the letter.
‎After the exhibition,
‎I'll respect the wishes of my late father,
‎the foundation's first director,
‎and donate it to his alma mater--
‎Great shot.
‎I'm playing decently today.
‎It's really nice.
‎A design that focuses
‎on harmonizing with nature.
‎The layout is daring too.
‎Is it Jackson Nicola's work?
‎I paid a small fortune
‎to get the design right.
‎Come and play often.
‎Just gather a solid group first.
‎Right.
‎You went to school with Cha Gi-u
‎from Cha & Yul Law Firm, right?
‎Yeah, he's one of our members.
‎Should I set up a round with him?
‎Sure.
‎Okay.
‎-I need to take this.
‎-Sure.
‎Hey, Yeo-ri.
‎Sure, let's go together.
‎I'll pick you up.
‎-What is it?
‎-Just get in there.
‎-Hurry up.
‎-What's this about?
‎Come on and sit over there.
‎And drink this. It's the latte you like.
‎Sit.
‎What's up?
‎Hey.
‎Tell me all you know
‎about what you said in the cafeteria.
‎About what?
‎The Reina Hotel slush fund.
‎Oh, that?
‎You want me to talk for free?
‎I got you coffee.
‎How about a meal?
‎A meal? I'll buy you food too.
‎Here. Drink this.
‎Not the cafeteria. Somewhere else.
‎Okay, fine.
‎What's the smoke you saw?
‎I'll pick the time and location then.
‎Deal. Now start talking.
‎This is perfect.
‎-We'll make it if we go now.
‎-Where?
‎You said I could decide
‎on the time and location.
‎Not right now. I have to work late.
‎Do that after eating with me.
‎-Come along.
‎-But…
‎-Hey, you really need to fix that.
‎-Hurry.
‎Let me get my coat.
‎This is where you wanted to eat?
‎Yeah. I wanted to come
‎to a place like this with you.
‎Hey, Gang-uk.
‎What the heck was that about?
‎This isn't my taste.
‎Let's go someplace else.
‎Then I'll forget all I know
‎about Reina Hotel and its slush fund.
‎What event are we here for?
‎That one.
‎You haven't heard of it?
‎It's been a hot topic lately.
‎They're hosting a special unveiling today
‎before showing it to the public.
‎How did you get invited
‎to something like this?
‎I got to know the director here
‎while investigating an art theft case.
‎You know, she set me up
‎on a few blind dates with some great guys.
‎You could've brought
‎one of them here instead.
‎-Why drag poor busy me here?
‎-You're not getting it, are you?
‎I wanted to bring you.
‎Fine, whatever.
‎Where are they showing that letter?
‎Probably somewhere indoors. Let's go.
‎It's so pretty.
‎WAITING FOR A LOVE LETTER AFTER 300 YEARS
‎Hey, I look horrible. Delete it.
‎No one told you to scowl.
‎-Hey.
‎-Wow.
‎So the 300-year-old love letter
‎is in that glass case?
‎It looks like it.
‎Prosecutor Im.
‎-Hello, Director.
‎-Hi.
‎Thank you for the invitation.
‎-Thanks so much for coming.
‎-Of course.
‎Who might this be?
‎He's a colleague of mine,
‎Prosecutor Ma Gang-uk.
‎-I see. Nice to meet you.
‎-It's a pleasure.
‎-Would you come and say hello?
‎-Sure.
‎-Let's go, Ma.
‎-What?
‎Let's go.
‎Yeo-ri.
‎Right.
‎-Let's go.
‎-Let go of me.
‎Yeo-ri.
‎Thank you for making
‎the long journey over.
‎I'm Lee Hwa-yong,
‎Director of the Yeeon Foundation.
‎-What are you looking at?
‎-Look straight ahead.
‎My late father built
‎the Yeeon Museum of Art
‎where Prince Gangpyeong's
‎residence once stood…
‎Why does he always stare at me like that?
‎It makes me emotional
‎that I can unveil the letter here today.
‎I will now unveil the love letter
‎of Hwagyeongdang,
‎who was a great poet of her time
‎and also a respected painter.
‎Is it breaking?
‎-It's about to crack.
‎-Oh, no!
‎Ms. Kim.
‎Our apologies.
‎This event is cancelled,
‎and we'll inform you of further plans.
‎We're very sorry.
‎Please stay calm.
‎You can take the stairs and exit safely.
‎We apologize for the disturbance.
‎Show them the way.
‎What on earth was that?
‎-Are you hurt?
‎-Moving a tomb can bring bad luck.
‎-Watch your step.
‎-Is that what happened?
‎It must be that.
‎Why would a glass case break
‎when no one touched it?
‎I know, right?
‎This doesn't feel right.
‎-It feels ominous.
‎-Let's get out of here.
‎Leave slowly, one at a time.
‎-What do you think happened?
‎-The glass shattered.
‎-What a shoddy job.
‎-Make sure you have your belongings.
‎-Why would a perfectly fine glass break?
‎-It felt so strange.
‎Aren't you coming?
‎I have to go somewhere.
‎-I'll come with you.
‎-No, no.
‎My stomach hurts.
‎I'm going to the bathroom.
‎-You go ahead. Bye.
‎-What?
‎I came here for a meeting
‎at my mother's request.
‎Can I quickly go and say hello?
‎Yeah, sure. Go ahead.
‎-Sorry. Look around in the meantime.
‎-Okay.
‎The legal team will file for damages
‎against the glass manufacturer.
‎Our apologies, ma'am.
‎What for?
‎Will you make them pay
‎for the broken glass?
‎Is this how you think
‎an unveiling should go?
‎What will you do about the humiliation?
‎What?
‎Oh, Mr. Kang.
‎-You must've been shocked earlier.
‎-Not at all.
‎We'll arrange another unveiling
‎to make up for it.
‎Okay.
‎Hey, Yeo-ri.
‎You're still here?
‎Yes.
‎I didn't get to properly say hi earlier
‎when we've met again after a while.
‎How have you been?
‎I've been doing fine, I guess.
‎So we meet again.
‎Are you doing well too?
‎Yes, of course. I'm great.
‎You seem to have solved
‎another case by the river.
‎That's what I do as usual.
‎Right.
‎Bye then.
‎Wait. Just a moment.
‎I'm not doing well, actually.
‎The thing is…
‎Are you unwell because of the accident?
‎No, it's not that.
‎I still see them.
‎I mean,
‎I still see ghosts and I'm struggling.
‎No way. That can't be.
‎I still see ghosts all the time,
‎and they give me a fright.
‎I wasn't sure
‎if I should contact you about it,
‎and we happened to meet here today.
‎Then…
‎do you see the ghost that's here with us?
‎What?
‎Yes, I see it.
‎What does it look like?
‎It's wearing ‎hanbok‎,
‎the traditional Korean outfit.
‎-What else?
‎Go on. What does it look like?
‎It's wearing a jade ‎binyeo‎,
‎that fancy hairpin, and is very graceful.
‎-What else?
‎Do you see a small black mole
‎under an eye?
‎Yes, I do. There's a mole under one eye.
‎-And is there a knife in her mouth?
‎-Yes. I feel her resentment.
‎She's glaring at me
‎with the knife in her mouth…
‎What prosecutor is this good at lying?
‎You could tell?
‎How did you know it was wearing ‎hanbok‎?
‎Well, this place
‎felt like the set of a period drama,
‎and those portraits stood out
‎the moment you asked.
‎And the jade ‎binyeo‎.
‎Where did that idea come from?
‎People wearing ‎hanbok
‎tend to wear one or two of them.
‎How did you catch on right away?
‎Because it's not a woman.
‎It's a man.
‎What?
‎Then is there really one…
‎next to me?
‎Yes, he's right next to you.
‎I'm sorry, I'll be careful.
‎Ms. Cheon,
‎is there something wrong with this place?
‎Well, I can't say for sure just yet.
‎I need to look into it some more.
‎Right. I see.
‎Ms. Cheon.
‎Why don't we work together?
‎On what?
‎I don't know what exactly,
‎but this feels huge and historical.
‎It might be better to cooperate
‎than to work on your own.
‎You can handle the dead,
‎and I can handle the living.
‎This is my thing.
‎I'm on the Cold Case Unit.
‎How about we work together--
‎You're still here?
‎Yes.
‎Think about it. I'll wait for your call.
‎Let's go.
‎Okay.
‎"You're still here?"
‎I need a beer.
‎Ms. Cheon.
‎Why don't we work together?
‎You can handle the dead,
‎and I can handle the living.
‎-Let's go, Ma.
‎-What?
‎Hey, Min-hwan.
‎It's me.
‎Director Ok,
‎should we acquire another masterpiece?
‎Pardon?
‎I like how our last purchase went.
‎It was the easiest to clean up.
‎Won't it be a bit too risky
‎to employ the same tactic twice?
‎You see, the thing is…
‎CEO KANG MIN-HWAN
‎Goodness, excuse me.
‎Hey, Mr. Kang.
‎Yes, what is it, Min-hwan?
‎What?
‎Cheon Yeo-ri did?
‎Ms. Cheon.
‎-Hello, I'm Cheon Yeo-ri.
‎-Goodness.
‎I didn't get to introduce myself
‎properly yesterday.
‎Oh, about that.
‎You must've been so disappointed.
‎-It was such a humiliation.
‎-Not at all.
‎I've hosted enough events to know
‎that things happen,
‎however well you're prepared.
‎Thank you for being so understanding.
‎I wondered why
‎you'd take so much interest
‎in something like this.
‎Min-hwan tells me you studied
‎Archaeology and Art History.
‎I assumed you'd have studied
‎Hotel Management or something like that.
‎Thank you for your time, Director.
‎Don't mention it.
‎You can ask me anything you want.
‎May I ask who drew these portraits?
‎Oh, yes.
‎That would be Dowon.
‎He wasn't acknowledged
‎or appreciated in his time.
‎Could I take another look
‎at the love letter?
‎Yes, of course.
‎Come this way.
‎If this was found while relocating
‎Prince Gangpyeong's tomb,
‎then was this love letter found
‎inside his coffin?
‎Yes.
‎Don't you find that so romantic?
‎He must've yearned for her so deeply
‎to have taken this letter
‎with him to death.
‎It would have been a scandal in their day.
‎Prince Gangpyeong was a royal
‎who loved a woman beneath his class,
‎a ‎gisaeng,‎ a courtesan,
‎enough to make her his second wife.
‎Where was Hwagyeongdang buried then?
‎According to the story
‎told over generations,
‎Prince Gangpyeong took her
‎on an excursion to Mt. Geumgang,
‎where Hwagyeongdang vanished
‎without‎ a ‎trace.
‎One version of the story says
‎she became an immortal hermit.
‎I suppose that's how legends are made.
‎Isn't it beautiful?
‎Even down in the south,
‎such bright red camellias are rare.
‎This isn't the time of year
‎for them to be in full bloom like that.
‎So for the flowers to bloom
‎all of a sudden
‎can only be a sign
‎of good things to come.
‎What do you mean by that?
‎The camellias must've known
‎that the love letter would be found.
‎Just look at that sight.
‎Here. Now get to it.
‎-It's just a rumor, okay?
‎-Okay.
‎A prosecutor went abroad
‎on a business trip
‎and bought a pretty expensive painting.
‎Since when do prosecutors do that?
‎It's verified that they bought a painting,
‎but there's no record of it
‎clearing customs.
‎If customs has no record of it,
‎then either it didn't enter the country
‎or someone powerful enough
‎to override customs was involved.
‎A diplomatic pouch or Air Force One?
‎That must've let off serious smoke.
‎Why didn't they dig further?
‎It's not that they didn't. They couldn't.
‎The person who bought the painting
‎was Chief Prosecutor Ok Gye-dong.
‎His older sister is Director Ok Gye-hui
‎of Reina Hotels & Resorts.
‎Do you see where this is going?
‎Does that mean Director Ok is involved
‎in Reina's money-laundering scheme?
‎Whether it's money laundering or bribery,
‎someone inside Reina
‎could be up to something.
‎No way. I knew it.
‎Knew what?
‎Look. They're birds of a feather.
‎REINA'S CHEON YEO-RI
‎DATING CL SUCCESSOR KANG MIN-HWAN
‎THE PAIR ATTENDED
‎AN OFFICIAL EVENT TOGETHER…
‎What the…
‎They were dating?
‎REINA'S CHEON YEO-RI
‎DATING CL SUCCESSOR KANG MIN-HWAN
‎You seem to have solved
‎another case by the river.
‎That's what I do as usual.
‎-Investigator Ko?
‎-Yes?
‎Have we been getting any tip-offs?
‎You know, like we did for Mt. Haewang
‎or the river body case.
‎No, we haven't gotten any recently.
‎Well, have you been slacking lately?
‎Or maybe things have
‎fallen through the cracks.
‎If you say that,
‎that would be my sign to burst into tears.
‎I'd be so hurt and upset.
‎I don't know what riled you up so badly
‎that you're taking it out on me…
‎-I'm not riled up.
‎-Okay.
‎We're supposed to solve cold cases,
‎but it's way too quiet.
‎Did you leave your post for hours
‎when you were on night duty?
‎-You too.
‎-What? No.
‎-Come on, man.
‎-What?
‎No, sorry. I mean, Mr. Ma.
‎Right. Mr. Ma.
‎If that's how you feel, from now on,
‎whenever I get a work call
‎or need to use the bathroom,
‎I'll call you to report
‎every single detail.
‎So that you're satisfied.
‎That's it.
‎That's why I must be involved,
‎even when it's you on night duty.
‎Be sure to call me
‎especially if you get any tip-offs.
‎Okay? You too, Hyeong-min.
‎-Yes, of course.
‎-Okay.
‎We'll work really hard.
‎I can see you.
‎Min-hwan said it wasn't him. Was it you?
‎Take a seat.
‎It's not a marriage announcement,
‎so what's the big deal?
‎-It's up by how many percent?
‎-Thirteen percent, ma'am.
‎My goodness.
‎That's how the market reacted
‎to Reina and CL.
‎You said you'd give me time.
‎And I will.
‎But I also need you
‎to give Min-hwan some hope.
‎Grandma.
‎-You can't barge in like that.
‎-I know what I'm doing.
‎I heard the news about you and Min-hwan
‎was the chairwoman's idea.
‎Did you ask her for a favor?
‎I must ask, only out of pure curiosity.
‎Are you doing this because
‎you really want to marry Min-hwan?
‎Why do you care?
‎This is insane.
‎It's nonsensical.
‎Why is it nonsensical?
‎So you ‎are‎ interested in marrying him.
‎Min-hwan and Ji-hwan were brothers.
‎If I were you, seeing Min-hwan
‎would remind me of Ji-hwan--
‎Cheon Ha-ri.
‎What?
‎That's enough. Get out.
‎NANGMAN SALTED BEEF TRIPE
‎No, you can't.
‎Go away. Leave.
‎Nice, pork skin.
‎Weren't they good last time?
‎That's one place,
‎and that's the other place.
‎We're spoiled with options.
‎You don't know
‎how addictive pork skin is.
‎Gang-uk, are you going for dinner?
‎-Hello.
‎-You're walking arm-in-arm?
‎-Are you eating out?
‎-Ms. Im, do you like pork skin?
‎-I love pork skin.
‎-Great, then we can…
‎How about we go over there?
‎Their pork skin is amazing.
‎-You should join us.
‎-Sounds good.
‎You can go and enjoy yourselves.
‎-We reserved a table…
‎-Come on in.
‎-Let's all eat together.
‎-I have to go.
‎Why leave when you came all this way?
‎I need to work late today.
‎You work late more often than you eat.
‎-Eat with us before you go.
‎-I'll just buy something on the way back.
‎Enjoy your meal
‎with Pil-dong and Hyeong-min.
‎-You're actually leaving?
‎-Enjoy yourself!
‎All right, attention!
‎Everyone who's waited for their turn,
‎show yourselves now.
‎Today, it's not first-come, first-served.
‎I'll pick based on your predicament.
‎"The vile one who got me
‎deserves nothing but a beating."
‎"I want to make sure
‎they pay the price and rot in prison."
‎Who has that kind of story?
‎Talk to me.
‎You first.
‎3 DAYS AGO
‎It was somewhere here.
‎Can we just call it a day and go home?
‎It looks like it'll rain soon,
‎and I have a bad feeling.
‎It's fine. I saw a really pretty one here.
‎-It's somewhere here.
‎-You did?
‎-You're sure it's nearby?
‎-This is it.
‎-Look.
‎-Really?
‎Wow.
‎You really found it.
‎It's beautiful.
‎Come and have a look.
‎Hello?
‎I should've stamped your fingerprint
‎before letting you go.
‎I forgot about that, honey.
‎WRITTEN WILL
‎Who's there?
‎Talk about killing someone twice.
‎How could one come back to do that?
‎A bastard like him
‎doesn't deserve to be human.
‎Are you on your own? This late at night?
‎Would I have come here with a lover,
‎this late at night?
‎If you're a passerby, just pass on by.
‎Why see something you shouldn't?
‎I wish I could unsee that too.
‎Oh, is that so?
‎Damn it.
‎You're not a bad fighter.
‎Who are you? Who the hell are you?
‎-Let go.
‎-Damn it.
‎I'll make you regret this.
‎What should I go for?
‎Your face?
‎You punk!
‎Get out of the way, Yeo-ri!
‎-Mr. Ma.
‎-Wait.
‎I'm fine. I'm fine, really.
‎Are you two an item?
‎You have a knife?
‎Damn it.
‎-That hurts.
‎-Keep still.
‎-Damn you.
‎-Are you okay, Yeo-ri?
‎Okay.
‎Let go of me, damn it!
‎I saw your face, you punk.
‎Sure, whatever.
‎Seeing ghosts
‎isn't some kind of superpower.
‎How can you be so fearless,
‎coming alone to a mountain this late?
‎That's why I called in a report
‎before coming here.
‎I cover all my bases
‎before I set in motion.
‎Right. Then what was that just now?
‎You could've been badly hurt
‎if not for me.
‎Aren't you the one
‎who could've been badly hurt?
‎How could you not even
‎land a kick properly?
‎That was a mistake.
‎I trained in taekwondo,
‎judo, hapkido, and boxing.
‎You don't know how fit I am.
‎Oh, you're so fit and well-trained
‎that you can't land a kick
‎when it actually counts?
‎I thought
‎you'd thrown out your back
‎because of the way you landed.
‎You're so cruel.
‎I was on standby for days on end,
‎working late in case you called.
‎You're not the police.
‎What prosecutor works late
‎to wait for a tip-off?
‎Are all prosecutors like that?
‎No other prosecutor does this.
‎I do it only because of you…
‎What I mean is…
‎I mean, I'm in charge of cold cases,
‎and we both used to see ghosts.
‎I can't just turn a blind eye.
‎Only my life is back to normal,
‎while you stay up at night
‎because of ghosts.
‎Right?
‎So from what I gather,
‎it looks like you're getting engaged
‎to your boyfriend.
‎It said we were dating,
‎not that we were engaged.
‎So it's true that you're dating him?
‎That false report will be corrected soon.
‎What? "False report"?
‎It's a false report?
‎Yes, and besides…
‎Why do you care if I'm dating or not?
‎You showed up to a special event
‎with your girlfriend proudly on your arm.
‎"Special event"?
‎You mean the art gallery?
‎I didn't link arms with her.
‎She clung to me like that.
‎She is not my girlfriend.
‎She and I are like…
‎We could never get close.
‎We're like the Earth and the moon.
‎That's how far apart we are.
‎-Like the Earth and the moon?
‎-Yes.
‎How lovely.
‎Those two always come as a pair.
‎Are you upset
‎that Im and I showed up as a pair?
‎I'm just stating a fact.
‎Did I say I was upset?
‎Well then, instead of
‎the Earth and the moon,
‎how about we call it Neptune?
‎Would you feel any less upset?
‎I never said I was upset.
‎Not that then.
‎Then how about Andromeda?
‎Andromeda sounds much better.
‎Doesn't it?
‎Is there anything farther away than that?
‎A black hole?
‎Not even a goodbye? Can't you at least…
‎Can't she at least say goodbye?
‎She didn't even bother.
‎You said you handled cold cases.
‎Yes.
‎Shall we take it on?
‎A 300-year-old cold case.
‎Let's work together.
‎FIND ME
‎SPOOKY IN LOVE
‎It's not the Joseon-era version of ‎Ghost,
‎but a total psychopath.
‎We'll do whatever it takes to find a way.
‎There's no such thing as a perfect crime.
‎What must be revealed will come to light.
‎I need you to check that.
‎That's the part that involves the living.
‎This looks more like
‎Ms. Cheon's part than mine.
‎Do you think Yeo-ri is actually onto us?
‎Yes, hello, Ms. Cheon.
‎Are these all the artworks
‎displayed around the hotel?
‎Why do you want to know that so badly?
‎What is this?
‎I got them on my business trip to Europe.
‎I thought they'd suit you.
‎I read the article about you two.
‎Congratulations.
‎Are Cheon Yeo-ri and Min-hwan
‎actually dating?
‎Min-hwan will be able to support you
‎more than enough.
‎Why are you so hard to reach?
‎You said you'd call me back.
‎I might have to get engaged.
‎What?
‎Subtitle translation by: Jennifer Jean Lim